in this segment we introduced a very
在这一部分，我们介绍了一个非常
central area of game theory called
博弈论的中心领域称为
mechanism design it's often called
机制设计，通常称为
so-called implementation theory and
所谓的实施理论和
sometimes also called inverse game
有时也称为逆向游戏
theory and the intuition is that when we
理论和直觉是，当我们
often think about game theory we think
经常想到我们认为的博弈论
about a given game that were somehow we
关于给定游戏的某种程度上，我们
inherit it it's a situation that we need
继承这是我们需要的情况
to reason about and so we do but in
进行推理，所以我们这样做，但是
mechanism design we get to design the
机制设计，我们来设计
game as so as to optimize for certain
游戏，以优化某些
qualities think for example about voting
素质例如考虑投票
we get to design the voting rules it can
我们可以设计投票规则
be plurality or plurality of elimination
被多个或多个消除
or border or pairwise elimination or any
或边界消除或成对消除或任何
number of other mechanisms or think
其他机制或思考的数量
about selling a product we can sell it
关于出售产品我们可以出售
directly by posting a price or we can
直接发布价格，或者我们可以
run an auction and there are many
进行拍卖，有很多
different kinds of auctions we could run
我们可以进行各种拍卖
these are all examples of mechanisms and
这些都是机制的例子，
we'll be speaking about how to model
我们将谈论如何建模
this formally and what mechanisms aim to
这是正式的，什么机制旨在
achieve so when we design a mechanism
当我们设计一种机制时实现
for example a voting rule we don't
例如我们没有投票规则
design it in a vacuum there are some set
在真空中设计有一些设置
of candidates for example that we don't
例如，我们不
get to control cannons will be what they
控制大炮将是他们
are
是
we certainly don't get to control who
我们当然不能控制谁
the voters are they are who they are and
选民是他们是谁，
we don't get to look inside their head
我们不要看他们的内心
and decide what they should care about
并决定他们应该关心什么
who they prefer to whom that's a given
他们更喜欢谁
that they're type also part of their
他们输入的内容也是他们的一部分
type are what their information or do
类型是他们的信息或行为
they know about various thing the
他们知道各种事情
setting we don't yet control any of that
设置我们还没有控制任何
so all that part all that background
所以所有的那部分背景
that we don't get to control is called
我们无法控制的被称为
the setting or the Bayesian game setting
设置或贝叶斯游戏设置
and what will happen and we'll go over
会发生什么，我们将结束
it now but what will happen is we'll be
现在，但是将会发生的事情是我们将
given a Bayesian game setting which
给定贝叶斯游戏设置
won't quite be a game be a setting and
不太会是游戏，而是场景
then we'll add to it the ingredient that
然后我们将添加到其中的成分
will turn it into a game and we'll try
将其变成游戏，我们将尝试
to design the game so as to optimize
设计游戏以进行优化
certain qualities and so so let's go
某些特质，所以让我们开始吧
over it we have this tuple and let's go
上面有这个元组，然后开始
over it in order so n is simply the set
按顺序排列，所以n只是集合
of agents and O is the set of outcomes
的代理人，O是结果集
so we have the social choice function
所以我们有社会选择功能
that has certain outcomes for example we
有一定的结果，例如我们
have a voting situation with certain
有一定的投票权
possible candidates and that is that
可能的候选人，那就是
said O then we have those types those
说哦，那么我们有那些类型
are the exactly the objects we saw in
正是我们看到的物体
Bayesian games again we don't yet have a
贝叶斯游戏再次，我们还没有
game here but the notion of type is well
游戏在这里，但类型的概念很好
defined and so we have and type really
定义，所以我们有并键入真正
all that private information to agents
给代理商的所有私人信息
so intuitively think about it as in the
所以像
voting situation what is my preference
投票情况我最喜欢什么
ordering about the candidates what do I
订购候选人我该怎么办
know about the preference ordering of
了解有关的偏好排序
other agents what do I know about what
其他代理我对什么了解
they know about my preference ordering
他们知道我的偏好排序
and all of that all that private
以及所有这些私有的
information is my type we have as we
信息是我们拥有的类型
usually do a common prior probability
通常做一个共同的先验概率
distribution over those types that's
分布在那些类型的
commonly known by the agent and we have
代理商通常知道的，我们有
a utility function that says given an
表示给定
outcome and given the types of the
结果和给定的类型
agents what is the utility to each of
代理商对每个人都有什么用处
the players and so given that my
球员，所以鉴于我
preference ordering is what it is and
偏好排序是什么，
given that a particular candidate was
鉴于特定的候选人是
elected for example
例如当选
would give me some utility this is all
会给我一些实用工具，这就是全部
the setting that we as mekin designers
我们作为设计师的环境
donate don't do not get to control and
捐赠不要不受控制，
don't have access to we know perhaps who
无法访问我们知道也许是谁
the agents are we don't know their types
代理商是我们不知道他们的类型
we we may know their the common prior on
我们可能知道他们的共同先验
those types so now what is the mechanism
这些类型，现在是什么机制
a mechanism consists of those things
一种机制包括那些东西
that when added to the Bayesian game
当添加到贝叶斯游戏中时
setting will make for a Bayesian game so
设置将使贝叶斯游戏如此
there's two things that missing are the
有两件事是
actions so so far we had no action for
到目前为止，我们还没有采取任何行动
the Able's so a mechanism simply
Able的机制如此简单
specifies the action for example the
指定操作，例如
voting rules or the auction rules and it
投票规则或拍卖规则及其
also specifies because the actions if
还指定了因为操作
they just live in a vacuum don't have
他们只是生活在真空中
any force so they need to interact with
任何力量，所以他们需要与
the Setting Sun while the action simply
夕阳，而行动只是
specify the the the outcome or more
指定结果或更多
generally a distribution of the outcome
通常结果的分布
so actions simply a set of actions for
所以动作只是一组动作
each of the agents for example in a
每个代理商，例如
voting situation it might be to specify
可能要指定投票情况
your entire ordering among the
您在整个订单中
candidates or to specify your top
候选人或指定您的最高职位
candidate whatever the voting rules are
候选人，无论投票规则如何
and a mapping says based on those
并根据这些内容进行映射
actions for example as votes who is the
例如作为选民的行动
winner and as you see a for technical
冠军，正如您所见，
reason we don't necessarily find one
我们不一定找到一个的原因
winner or one so for choice outcome but
获胜者或一个这样的选择结果，但
a distribution over those outcomes often
这些结果的分布通常
for your intuition think of it as
为了您的直觉，将其视为
specifying a specific outcome you worked
指定您工作的特定结果
you usually won't lose any intuition you
你通常不会失去任何直觉
think about it that way and so this is a
这样想，所以这是一个
mechanism given a Bayesian game setting
给定贝叶斯游戏设置的机制
you add these two ingredients the
您添加这两种成分
actions and how they map to outcomes and
行动及其与结果的对应关系，以及
when you put those together you get a
当你把它们放在一起时，你会得到一个
patient game so how do you specify the
耐心的游戏，那么您如何指定
mechanism well the intuition is that we
很好的直觉是我们
want to
想要
we want the agent to behave a certain
我们希望代理人表现出一定的行为
way we would like to reach a certain
我们想达成的目标
software choice outcome that's best for
最适合的软件选择结果
example we might want to find a socially
例如我们可能想找到一个社交
optimal Pareto efficient outcome we
最优帕累托有效结果
might want in an auction set in two
可能希望将拍卖分为两部分
layers to auction setting to maximize
拍卖设置最大化
our revenue and do that while not having
我们的收入，而没有
control over the bathing game setting
控制沐浴游戏的设置
and so the trick is to set up the rules
所以诀窍是建立规则
of the game the mechanism to cause agent
游戏的致使机制
to behave the way we want them even
表现出我们想要他们的方式
though we don't have access to the
尽管我们无权访问
internal information and can directly
内部信息并可以直接
control the actions but we will set the
控制动作，但我们将设置
rules of the game such that by their
这样的游戏规则
acting in their own perceived
以自己的感觉行事
self-interest they will lead to the
出于自身利益，他们将导致
outcome we desire and so it's really an
我们想要的结果，所以这真的是
operative do it in a number of ways as
操作性地通过多种方式做到这一点
you can think of it as a an optimization
您可以将其视为优化
problem with only partial information
仅部分信息的问题
about and control over the variables
关于和控制变量
you're optimizing you can think of it as
您正在优化，可以将其视为
a you could think of the the setting as
一个你可以想到的设置
a set of Bayesian game and you're
一组贝叶斯游戏，
picking a selecting a particular
选择一个特定的
Bayesian game out of the set and really
贝叶斯游戏超出了预期
perhaps the most basic view of it is
也许最基本的看法是
goes back to one of the terms
回到其中一项
implementation theory and we really want
实施理论，我们真的想要
to implement a social choice function
实施社会选择功能
which we if we had access to the agents
如果我们可以与代理商联系
type we could have done directly but we
类型我们可以直接完成，但是我们
don't if we simply ask the agents it may
不要只问代理商
not invade may be in their interest to
不入侵可能符合他们的利益
deceive us and so our goal is to
欺骗我们，所以我们的目标是
implement it nonetheless and so
尽管如此，还是执行它
something magical about the setting and
关于设置的神奇之处
it's a quite a robust area within game
这是游戏中相当强大的区域
theory so what does it mean to implement
理论，那么实施意味着什么
a social choice function it in fact has
它实际上具有的社会选择功能
several possible
几种可能
one of them among the strongest is
其中最强的之一是
implementation in dominant strategies
主导策略的实施
what does that mean well let's assume we
这意味着什么，让我们假设我们
start with the Bayesian game setting and
从贝叶斯游戏设置开始
we add to it a mechanism and we'll say
我们添加了一种机制，我们会说
that that mechanism implements a social
该机制实现了社会
choice function C in dominant strategy
主导策略中的选择函数C
if it's the case that take any utility
如果是这种情况需要任何实用程序
function for the agent any vector U of
代理的任何向量U
utility functions one for each of the
实用程序功能每个
agents if the game has an equilibrium in
代理商，如果博弈在
dominant strategies such that in any
这样的主导策略
such equilibrium because there could be
这样的平衡，因为可能
multiple in dominant strategy but any
主导策略的倍数，但任何
such equilibrium we have that the
这样的平衡，我们有
outcome specified by the mechanism is
该机制指定的结果是
indeed a social choice function with in
确实具有
that case we will say that the mick
那样的话，我们会说米克
isn't implemented the solar choice
没有实现太阳能的选择
function in dominant strategies you
在主导策略中发挥作用
could ask several questions about it why
可以问几个问题，为什么
should it be in all equilibrium maybe
是否应该处于完全平衡状态
it's enough that in one indeed you could
这足以使您确实可以
define it that way
这样定义
why only dominant strategies and in fact
为什么只有主导策略，实际上
the answer is it doesn't have to be in
答案是不必一定要
dominant strategy so the more a more
主导策略，所以越多
general more relaxed definition of
一般更宽松的定义
implementation is implication in a Bayes
在贝叶斯中实现
Nash equilibrium and it is almost the
纳什均衡，它几乎是
same we say that given this patient game
同样，我们说，鉴于这场耐心的比赛
setting will say that the mechanism
设置会说机制
implements the social choice function in
实施社会选择功能
a Bayes Nash equilibrium as opposed to
贝叶斯纳什均衡而不是
dominant strategy equilibrium if there
如果存在主导策略均衡
exists a Bayes Nash equilibrium of the
存在一个贝叶斯纳什均衡
game that results from the mechanism in
机制产生的游戏
the setting such that in for every
这样的设置
type of agents and every action profile
代理类型和每个操作配置文件
that can arise in this equilibrium it's
在这种平衡中可能会出现
the case that the outcome defined by
如果结果定义为
that action profile is a social choice
行动概况是一种社会选择
function of the agents given their types
给定其类型的代理的功能
so it's a at a little bit of a mouthful
所以只需要一点点
here but the intuition is very much the
在这里，但直觉非常
same as in the dominant strategy
与主导策略相同
implementation in dominant strategies
主导策略的实施
the situation is simple we simply have
情况很简单，我们只需
dominant strategies and we require that
主导策略，我们要求
in all of those the action profile lead
在所有这些动作简介中
to a softer choice function here we have
一个更柔和的选择功能
probability distributions and so there
概率分布等
can be multiple actions that instantiate
可以是多个实例化的动作
despite these these these the action
尽管这些这些这些行动
profile of these strategies and what we
这些策略的概况以及我们
want it be the case that every action
希望每个动作都这样
profile would lead up by definition to
配置文件将导致定义为
some outcome according to the this
根据这个结果
mapping and we would like to be the case
映射，我们希望如此
that indeed is a social choice of the
那确实是社会的选择
agents and they are meaning they have
代理商，他们的意思是他们有
their own preferences and with respect
自己的喜好和尊重
to those preferences we want that action
根据这些偏好，我们希望该操作
profile to lead to the optimal outcome
剖面以达到最佳效果
as defined by the social choice function
由社会选择功能定义
so as I said earlier mechanism design is
正如我之前所说，机制设计是
a very rich and deep topic in game
游戏中一个非常丰富而深刻的话题
theory there's a lot to say about it
理论上有很多话要说
both from the follower point of view and
从追随者的角度来看
it's also among that parts of game
这也是游戏的一部分
theory that have lent themselves most to
最适合自己的理论
applications most nodes will be two
应用程序大多数节点将是两个
options and there are separate lectures
选项，并有单独的讲座
about that but let me for now stay at
关于这个，但让我暂时留在
kind of more abstract level and make a
比较抽象的层次，
few comments about business
关于业务的一些评论
implementation first of all there could
首先可以实现
be multiple equilibria and we back to
是多重均衡，我们回到
the same issue that we haven't game
我们没有玩过的相同问题
theory in general even before we speak
一般的理论，甚至在我们说话之前
about making the design when we have
关于我们进行设计时
multiple equilibria of a game what do we
游戏的多重均衡我们该怎么办
actually predict that will happen now in
实际预测那会发生在
a maximum design setting we could say if
我们可以说最大设计设置
I have multiple equilibria is it enough
我有多个平衡点就够了
that I select one of them and require
我选择其中之一并要求
that the at equilibrium always lead to
处于平衡状态总是导致
social choice optimum or or not we have
社会选择的最佳与否
the usual concerns about a career in
人们对职业的普遍关注
general equilibrium is very strong
总体平衡很强
notion what happens if agents first of
如果代理商首先
all somehow miss coordinate on the
都以某种方式错过了协调
equilibria and play different says that
平衡和发挥不同说
the strategy profiles corresponding to
对应的策略配置文件
different equilibria or even more
不同的平衡甚至更多
extremely don't play an equilibrium at
极端不平衡
all a legitimate question in game theory
博弈论中所有合理的问题
general and in particular here also
一般，特别是这里
equilibria a very general category and
均衡是一个非常笼统的类别
one one one one objection could be that
一对一反对可能是
asymmetric equilibria are implausibly
非对称的平衡是令人难以置信的
here there's no reason to think that
这里没有理由认为
representing game one one agent would
代表一场比赛的一位特工
gravitate to one strategy and another
倾向于一种策略而另一种
agent to another even though the setting
即使设置也可以代理
is confusing
令人困惑
and so there are various things you
所以你有很多事情
could do about these questions and
可以解决这些问题，
concerns one of them is simply required
只是其中之一
that the implementation be asymmetric
实现不对称
based national program that takes care
基于国家的照顾计划
of the asymmetry concerns you might want
您可能想要的不对称问题
also to require exposed implementation
还要求公开实施
meaning that the strategies selected are
表示选择的策略是
an exposed equilibrium a very strong
暴露的平衡非常强
notion so agent don't experience regret
代理人不会后悔的想法
for having selected those Olivia even
甚至选择了那些奥利维亚
after the game is played go beyond
游戏结束后，超越
issues specific to bathe Nash
沐浴纳什的特定问题
implementation on implementation of
实施
solar choice functions in general we can
一般我们可以选择太阳能
require indeed that it arrives in some
确实要求它到达一些
equilibrium or in every equilibrium we
平衡或我们在每个平衡中
can even require that there be only one
甚至可以要求只有一个
equilibrium in which it requires and
它需要的平衡和
finally there's various ways to have to
终于有各种各样的方法
implement the function and one important
实现功能和一个重要
distinction that to keep in mind is
要记住的区别是
between direct implementation and
在直接实施和
indirect implementation in a direct
直接执行中的间接执行
implementation agents send essentially a
实施代理实质上发送了
single message to the mechanism designer
给机制设计者的一条消息
the center disclosing whatever they need
中心披露他们需要的一切
to disclose about their type and then
透露他们的类型，然后
the rest happens in within the mechanism
其余的发生在机制内
whereas indirect mechanisms there's a an
而间接机制有一个
iterative process of messaging back and
回传消息的迭代过程
forth think even about voting as an
甚至考虑将投票作为
example you could simply disclose once
例如，您只需披露一次
and for all something for example your
对于所有事物，例如您的
entire preference profile for A to C to
A到C的整个偏好设置
B or if the mechanism calls for only
B或该机制仅要求
disclosing your top choice a I simply
公开您的首选a我只是
prefer a to the others and that's it
比其他人更喜欢一个
that'll be a direct
那将是直接的
mechanism whereas an iterative mechanism
机制，而迭代机制
would say for example in a you know
例如会说
voting situation might say so you know
投票情况可能会说，所以你知道
as I speak about parameters elimination
当我谈到参数消除时
you declare a tough choice and then
你宣布一个艰难的选择，然后
again you declare the top choice among
再次声明您是其中的首选
the remaining candidates and and and you
其余的候选人和以及您
might there be an unfolding process
可能会有一个展开的过程
direct implementations will turn out to
直接实现将变成
be quite Universal in what they can
尽其所能
accomplish and much easier to analyze
完成并且更容易分析
the indirect implementation and so for
间接实现等
theoretical investigation purposes at
的理论研究目的
least they are quite central
至少他们很重要